

## CONTACT

404-345-4187 jessa.clark@icloud.com www.creativejessa.com

# **EDUCATION**

General Assembly 2021

Certificate, Computer Software Engineering

Ashford University 2014 - 2016

B.S., Complementary and Alternative Health

lvy Tech 2015 - 2016

TC, Office Administration

# **SKILLS**

HTML

CSS

JavaScript

React

SQL

#### FRONT END DEVELOPER

## **ABOUT ME**

Front End Developer with 4 years of experience in designing and developing inclusive user interfaces, branding and business management. A natural leader and enthusiastic collaborator who is driven by curiosity, problem-solving and crafting innovative solutions.

### **EXPERIENCE**

### Sales Execution Coordinator

Eagle Rock Distributing Company (2021 to present)

- Analyzes and reports on sales, providing analysis and developed insights around KPI's
- Assist sales team in developing new forecasting models and data visualizations.
- Built custom dashboards within ERP by using HTML, JS, CSS
- Coordinates sales division, working with management to prioritize needs.

## Software Engineering Fellow

General Assembly (2021)

- Built full responsive web applications using HTML, CSS, JavaScript, React and third-party API's
- Developed full stack applications and designed REST API's with full CRUD functionality using MongoDB, Express, React and Node (MERN)
- Managed team-based projects using Git version control, Figma and Slack.

### C.E.O

MaJiC Innovations, Inc. (2018 - 2021)

- Owned and operated business.
- Developed online store, website and branding using Square, Wix, Wordpress and Canva.
- Managed financials, sales, marketing, web design and social media. for multiple businesses.